I don't care how much you were involved,
or what your relationship with that woman is.
I will forgive your rebellion this time.
Father.
Thank you for your forgiveness.
Thank you
for always thinking of me.
You really are a good father.
So,
you did all this.
December 1st.
Yesterday.
It was Chenyao.
This...
Chenyao.
What?
You said the things you forced me to do in the past
were instigated by your father.
Qianqian.
How long have you been with me?
Two years.
You've become the most trusted person by my side.
It's all because Mr. Ling
intentionally cultivated me.
We are the same.
We stop at nothing to achieve our goals.
You don't hesitate to use your own sister
as a tool.
You've secretly made off with a lot of clients' money, haven't you?
Mr. Ling.
I...
I know why you did this.
Mucheng's position back then
should have belonged to your sister.
Do something for me.
I will make your sister the top star,
and give you half of the company's shares.
Don't move.
Why are you here?
How about
we try again?
Actually,
things might still turn around.
I don't know what you're trying to do.
Stop right there.
All the cases you're involved in,
I'll take the blame for you.
Also,
that media company,
I'll give you all the shares.
I just need you to get the notebook back for me.
Dear Father,
I don't understand what you're saying.
Just serve your sentence in peace,
confess your crimes,
and truly repent.
I will definitely take good care of the company for you.
Not just that media company,
but the entire group.
I'll take good care of all of it.
By the way,
don't forget,
I
am your biological son.
And,
I will also definitely
take good care of my own brother.
Congratulations.
All of this is finally coming to an end.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just feel like ever since you appeared,
everything has become so dreamy.
Even now, I often wonder
if all of this
is really just a dream.
Thank you.
For what?
Everything.
Thank you, too.
For what?
Because of you,
after a thousand years,
I suddenly feel alive again.
Really?
Of course.
Who taught you to be so cheesy?
I'm telling the truth.
Why do I feel
that since we came back,
something is weird?
What's weird?
Every time I get close to you, I feel
like we're so familiar,
like we've known each other for a long time.
But
there's also a hint of...
What?
Regret,
and a bit of anger.
I can't explain it.
Chen Yao,
did you promise my dad
that if one day
I can stand on my own,
you would leave?
Yes.
I mean,
is it possible for you not to leave?
Don't leave Tang'er behind, okay?
I'm not trying to force you to stay.
Aren't you a spirit?
To you, my life is so short.
Why don't you just be a good guy to the end
and stay with me for the rest of my life?
I'm just kidding.
Did you take it seriously?
Since you appeared when I was at my weakest
and let me rely on you,
the rest of my life should be the same.
Please don't go.